

ARTHUR SPLAVSKYI

Frontend Developer

PORTFOLIO arthursplavskiy.netlify.app

WORK EXPERIENCE (more than 3 years)

Frontend Developer. Travellizy. Odessa. travellizy.com

SEP 2022 - MAY 2023

Development of a new corporate website, support of company projects.

Frontend Developer. Increate. Kyiv. in-create.com

MAR 2021 - PRESENT

Development of corporate websites, creative websites for awwwards, support of existing projects.

Web programmer. Testrite. Kyiv. testrite.com.ua

JAN 2021 - MAR 2021

Corporate site support. Development of new modules.

Freelance

OCT 2018 - MAR 2019

Developed landing page sites and refined existing sites. Worked with a backend developer and designer.

PROFILE

I have more than 3 years of experience in front-end development. I was mainly engaged in JavaScript/HTML/CSS development and creation of creative websites for awwwards. I actively use the React library and the Next framework, I use these and other libraries to develop SPA applications, corporate and e-Commerce sites.

Strengths:

- 1. Responsible;
- 2. Very responsible;
- 3. Honest and Direct;
- 4. Calm and Practical;

Weaknesses:

- 1. Difficulties in communicating complex ideas clearly;
- 2. Waste of resources due to excessive scrupulousness;
- 3. Ability to show indifference to others, be overly critical and demanding;

Goal: Developing a product that is useful for people. Grow to a team leader position in 5-6 years.

SKILLS



Node.js Gulp Webpack WebGL GreenSock

Languages: English (middle).

EDUCATION

Junior Specialist at technical college. Kamenets-Podilskiy

2016 - 2020

Higher Education (incomplete). NUHT. Kyiv

2020 - 2022

WEBSITES & SOCIAL LINKS

Phone: +38 (096) 4751 567

Email: arthur.splavskiy@gmail.com

Telegram: https://t.me/arthursplavskiy

GitHub: https://github.com/ArthurSplavskiy

Portfolio: https://arthursplavskiy.netlify.app/

Instagram: instagram.com/arthur.splavskiy